(Raj:)Hey.
(Amy:)Hey, what's going on?
Not much.
(Bernadette:)You want to get a drink later?
(Bernadette:)Just the two of us?
(Amy:)No Penny?
(Bernadette:)Not tonight.
(Bernadette:)I'm a little frustrated
with her.
(Amy:)Because you got her the job
and you think
(Amy:)she should be working harder
to prepare for it?
(Bernadette:)So it's not just me.
You see it, too!
(Amy:)I do, I see it.
(Bernadette:)It's driving me crazy.
(Bernadette:)Just this afternoon,
I saw on Instagram
(Bernadette:)that instead of studying,
she went out to lunch
(Bernadette:)and got a manicure.
That's outrageous!
I know!
(Amy:)If she doesn't do well,
th-this could reflect poorly
on you.
(Bernadette:)Exactly. Does she not realize it
or does she not care?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Amy:)The important thing is
I am here for you
(Amy:)so we can mutually disparage
this unpleasing third party.
(Leonard:)Hey. We just wanted to see
(Leonard:)how your class was going.
Where is everybody?
(Sheldon:)There is no class.